export const quizdata = [
	{
		question: 'Who was elected President of the United States in 2017?',
		choices: ['2005', '2008', '2010', '2012'],
		answer: '2008',
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the name of Thor’s hammer?',
		choices: ['Vanir', 'Mjolnir', 'Aesir', 'Norn'],
		answer: 'Mjolnir',
	},
	{
		question:
			' In the Incredible Hulk, what does Tony tell Thaddeus Ross at the end of the film?',
		choices: [
			'That he wants to study The Hulk',
			'That he knows about S.H.I.E.L.D.',
			'That they are putting a team together',
			'That Thaddeus owes him money',
		],
		answer: 'That they are putting a team together',
	},
	{
		question: 'What is Captain America’s shield made of?',
		choices: ['Adamantium', 'Vibranium', 'Promethium', 'Carbonadium'],
		answer: 'Vibranium',
	},
	{
		question:
			'The Flerkens are a race of extremely dangerous aliens that resembles what?',
		choices: ['Cats', 'Ducks', 'Reptiles', 'Raccoons'],
		answer: 'Cats',
	},
	{
		question:
			'Before becoming Vision, what is the name of Iron Man’s A.I. butler?',
		choices: ['H.O.M.E.R.', 'J.A.R.V.I.S.', 'A.L.F.R.E.D.', 'M.A.R.V.I.N.'],
		answer: 'J.A.R.V.I.S',
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the real name of the Black Panther?',
		choices: ['T’Challa', 'M’Baku', 'N’Jadaka', 'N’Jobu'],
		answer: 'T’Challa',
	},
	{
		question:
			'What is the alien race Loki sends to invade Earth in The Avengers?',
		choices: ['The Chitauri', 'The Skrulls', 'The Kree', 'The Flerkens'],
		answer: 'The Chitauri',
	},
	{
		question:
			'Who was the last holder of the Space Stone before Thanos claims it for his Infinity Gauntlet?',
		choices: ['Thor', 'Loki', 'The Collector', 'Tony Stark'],
		answer: 'Loki',
	},
	{
		question: 'What fake name does Natasha use when she first meets Tony?',
		choices: [
			'Natalie Rushman',
			'Natalia Romanoff ',
			'Nicole Rohan',
			'Naya Rabe',
		],
		answer: 'Natalie Rushman',
	},
	{
		question: ' What does Thor want another of when he’s in the diner?',
		choices: [
			'A slice of pie',
			'A pint of beer',
			'A stack of pancakes',
			'A cup of coffee',
		],
		answer: 'A cup of coffee',
	},
	{
		question:
			'Where does Peggy tell Steve she wants to meet him for a dance, before he plunges into the ice?',
		choices: [
			'The Cotton Club',
			'The Stork Club',
			'El Morocco',
			'The Copacabana',
		],
		answer: ' The Stork Club',
	},
	{
		question: 'About which city do Hawkeye and Black Widow often reminisce?',
		choices: ['Budapest', 'Prague', 'Istanbul', 'Sokovia'],
		answer: 'Budapest',
	},
	{
		question: 'Who does the Mad Titan sacrifice to acquire the Soul Stone?',
		choices: ['Nebula', 'Ebony Maw', 'Cull Obsidian', 'Gamora'],
		answer: 'Gamora',
	},
	{
		question:
			'What is the name of the little boy Tony befriends while stranded in the Iron Man 3?',
		choices: ['Harry', 'Henry', 'Harley', 'Holden'],
		answer: 'Harley',
	},
	{
		question:
			'Where do Lady Sif and Volstagg keep the Reality Stone after the Dark Elves tried to steal it?',
		choices: [
			'On Vormir',
			'In a vault on Asgard',
			'Inside Sif’s sword',
			'To the Collector',
		],
		answer: 'To the Collector',
	},
	{
		question:
			'What does the Winter Soldier say after Steve recognizes him for the first time?',
		choices: [
			'“Who the hell is Bucky?”',
			'“Do I know you?”',
			'“He’s gone.”',
			'“What did you say?”',
		],
		answer: '“Who the hell is Bucky?”',
	},
	{
		question:
			'What were the three items Rocket claims he needs in order to escape the prison?',
		choices: [
			'A security card, a fork, and an ankle monitor',
			'A security band, a battery, and a prosthetic leg',
			'A pair of binoculars, a detonator, and a prosthetic leg',
			'A knife, cable wires, and Peter’s mixtape',
		],
		answer: 'A security band, a battery, and a prosthetic leg',
	},
	{
		question: ' What word does Tony utter that makes Steve say, “Language”?',
		choices: ['“Crap!”', '“Asshole!”', '“Shit!”', '“Idiot!”'],
		answer: '“Shit!”',
	},
	{
		question:
			'What animal does Darren Cross unsuccessfully shrink in the Ant-Man?',
		choices: ['Mouse', 'Sheep', 'Duck', 'Hamster'],
		answer: 'Sheep',
	},
];
